const mathData = {
    Easy: [
      { question: "What is 2 + 2?", options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"], correctAnswer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 5 - 3?", options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], correctAnswer: "2" },
      { question: "What is 10 / 2?",options: ["2", "3", "5", "7"], correctAnswer: "5" },
      { question: "What is 3 * 3?", options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"], correctAnswer: "9" },
      { question: "What is 7 + 1?", options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"], correctAnswer: "8" },
      { question: "What is 6 - 2?", options: ["2", "3", "4", "5"], correctAnswer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 8 / 4?", options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"], correctAnswer: "2" },
      { question: "What is 4 * 2?", options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"], correctAnswer: "8" },
      { question: "What is 9 + 0?", options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"], correctAnswer: "9" },
      { question: "What is 5 - 1?", options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"], correctAnswer: "4" }
    ],
    Medium: [
      { question: "What is 12 + 15?", options: ["25", "26", "27", "28"], correctAnswer: "27" },
      { question: "What is 20 - 8?", options: ["10", "11", "12", "13"], correctAnswer: "12" },
      { question: "What is 15 / 3?", options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"], correctAnswer: "5" },
      { question: "What is 7 * 6?", options: ["40", "41", "42", "43"], correctAnswer: "42" },
      { question: "What is 18 + 7?", options: ["24", "25", "26", "27"], correctAnswer: "25" },
      { question: "What is 30 - 12?", options: ["16", "17", "18", "19"], correctAnswer: "18" },
      { question: "What is 24 / 4?", options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"], correctAnswer: "6" },
      { question: "What is 9 * 3?", options: ["26", "27", "28", "29"], correctAnswer: "27" },
      { question: "What is 14 + 9?", options: ["22", "23", "24", "25"], correctAnswer: "23" },
      { question: "What is 21 - 7?", options: ["12", "13", "14", "15"], correctAnswer: "14" }
    ],
    Hard: [
      { question: "What is 45 + 36?", options: ["80", "81", "82", "83"], correctAnswer: "81" },
      { question: "What is 56 - 19?", options: ["36", "37", "38", "39"], correctAnswer: "37" },
      { question: "What is 72 / 8?", options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"], correctAnswer: "9" },
      { question: "What is 13 * 7?", options: ["90", "91", "92", "93"], correctAnswer: "91" },
      { question: "What is 64 + 29?", options: ["92", "93", "94", "95"], correctAnswer: "93" },
      { question: "What is 81 - 23?", options: ["56", "57", "58", "59"], correctAnswer: "58" },
      { question: "What is 99 / 11?", options: ["8", "9", "10", "11"], correctAnswer: "9" },
      { question: "What is 17 * 5?", options: ["84", "85", "86", "87"], correctAnswer: "85" },
      { question: "What is 78 + 15?", options: ["92", "93", "94", "95"], correctAnswer: "93" },
      { question: "What is 100 - 45?", options: ["54", "55", "56", "57"], correctAnswer: "55" }
    ]
  }
  
  export default mathData